Hey, everybody
Julia's, she's rushing, she's coming, she's rushing, she's going so fast, I see her shadow
I saw the shadow of you running down the hallway
She's getting a drink and she's calling a cab and she's having a smoke and she's taking a drag
She was frantically looking for her wife
Where is she?
I climbed so- I fell through so many stairs
Through so many holes, they shoved my arm in so many holes
So much goop on your arm
Hi, Nathan, thanks for the raid
Hi, Nathan
Appreciate it, Nathan
I'm sorry to have rushed you, Julia
It's okay
Julia had to go to the bathroom unexpectedly, as many of us on this stream do right after the stream starts
Yeah
It's a thing that happens sometimes
Well, okay, so especially when you're pregnant,
You're what?
We keep getting people who are like
We keep getting people who
find out in really roundabout ways and they're like, they'll make a joke about me being pregnant and they're like, haha, it sounds like you're pregnant and I'm like
Like, do they know?
Yeah
Yeah, I am. Anyway, when you're pregnant, sometimes
you like very suddenly have to use the bathroom
Yeah, that's true. And sometimes I just have to use the bathroom really suddenly
Just in general
Yeah, sorry about that
When it hits, it hits, you know?
I was going to make a whole drink
When it hits, we shits. That's how we do it here
Kind of what happened
There's no shame in our game
I'm entering my mullet era
Don't jud
No, it looks good with like the... you put some product in. -I did, yeah. -Yeah, you got like the slick back. -Yeah. -I think it looks nice
I did, yeah
Yeah. -I think it looks nice. -I was like, I gotta go
Yeah
So yeah
Because you're trying to grow it back out, right?
Yeah, a little bit
So you can't
Short thing
Short bang
A nice short thing
Well, guess what? We're here
Yeah
Oh, wait, somebody said that because of my draw class, they were able to set up OBS and try their hand at streaming. Yay!
Yeah!
That's awesome
That is awesome. I'm glad that class was helpful to someone because it's one where like when I was in the middle of it, I was like, I feel like I'm in the weeds here
Right
I was like, I feel like I'm really... I forgot going in how much detail there is
Yeah
And then I was like, I don't know if anyone's going to, if this is going to mean anything to anyone
But all I can do is continue. I have to keep going to the other side
Sometimes when I make a draw class, I
I lose
sight of what I'm supposed to be teaching
People are like, hey, can you teach a horror class? And I'm like, yeah, sure. But then I'm like, what is horror? It depends on like the story
depends on what you're trying to portray
It's so true, both cats are showing up
And I'm like
Then I'm like, I guess what they're asking is like body horror, but like
That's not scary to everyone, that's not what was asked, I was asked to do horror
What about emotional horror?
What about like setting the tension? What about the payoff? -What about establishing a norm and then subverting it?
I got this jacket
about 10 years ago
uh, from Bass Outlet
Bass
Bias. Depends, this is a Kevin James Stanton
I thought you were just going to say Kevin James
This is a Kevin James
It's a Kevin James original
I don't know if y'all know this, but Kevin James, he tables at a lot of small cons and events
This was given to us by some people we were tabling near at Mocha. -It says, be good, do good, and I felt like that's always what I strive for
This one's from some shitty YouTube channel, and then this one's from some show they do on the shitty YouTube channel, so
You know, whatever
Julia loves representing shitty YouTube channels
I love it, I have money in this jacket
Money? How much?
Ten
11, 12
11, 12, 13
That's big sandwich money right there. -You could get a big sandwich for that amount
That is a big sandwich money
Woo! Put that right in my pocket, so I'll forget about it later
Huge, huge for us
Um, I... someone... some may say
that will be done with Silent Hill today
I don't know if that's true or not though. -It's going to be this one or the next one, I think
Well, I wore this outfit in case it was the last one
Did you see that Khaz made the Matrix edit and put it on our YouTube shorts?
I did not
I didn't know till I was sitting here looking at chat and someone in chat was talking about it and then I went and watched it, it's great
I'm scared too
Kaz came through
That's awesome
So we have the Morpheus
he's beginning to believe at it with James dodging pyramid head
Oh, that's great, I'm excited to watch it
And it's really funny with the seriousness of Morpheus saying he's beginning to believe and then us just like crying, laughing while James just dodges over and over against a wall
Yeah
Uh, yeah, I was legitimately like crying with laughter
Um, let's get into it, I guess
Y'all play the game
Got to unmute this
It's never a good energy to like run into the stream
It's like
No, you feel like you weren't like mentally
No, I feel... I feel discombobulated
You feel frazzled
I feel frazzled, that's a good word
I feel like I should say too going into this that like I'm like stupid today
I'm just not... I keep making little mistakes today, I keep doing dumb stuff
It's okay, I've been... I keep telling... well, Jacob and I both fell asleep at the same time in different rooms
And then I woke up from my nap and then I was like, immediately, I could go back to bed
I've been playing Dragon Age, so I felt like I could dodge into those barrels
You can keep going, this doesn't affect you at all
I was wondering if I would have to take over, you know
Take a... Oh, with the mouse
Yeah, yeah, yeah, since you have Olive
Is it boat time?
I think I'm supposed to take this bow
You're going to take this bag?
I'm gonna take that boat once I see if there's any ammo here
I was thinking today that like lately I feel like for those of you who are
Brandon Sanderson, Stormlight Archive Readers, I have not started the new book yet
Road trip
That's a shitty road trip, man
I've not started the new book yet and this is not a spoiler, but oftentimes I feel like
Um
In that book series, there's a character called Teravangian or Teravangian, I don't know how you pronounce his name
But one of his whole things is that like some days he wakes up and he's like a super genius and then other days most of the time he wakes up and he's like,
a dumbass, I've been feeling like him lately, where some days I wake up and I'm like, I'm just stupid today
And then other days I wake up and I'm like, I'm the smartest man who ever lived, I can do anything
But it's happening less and less
less and less I wake up and feel like the smartest man who ever lived, -and more and more I wake up and feel like a big idiot
I was trying to show our sister-in-law something and
I was like, I cannot remember where I put this thing. -I was like, my brain's been in the trash and she was like, -Oh, you're never getting it back
I was like, okay, cool
The brain is gone
Can I run? There we go
All right, this is going to be a cutscene, so
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Let's lock in
It's me
I'm the bad man
I'm on a boat starts playing
Oh
Boy
Who's ready to paddle?
Right on
the game we were playing where you're in a boat and you're rowing and then like a swamp witch and
keeps coming up and trying to get you. -Does that bramble?
Oh
Yeah
That's not going to happen in this one
I hear something
Isn't there like nothing out here?
I'm trying to remember from my
Well, we're going to discover that together
Just rowing forever
I keep hearing little sounds
Yeah, it's actually very interesting
Go towards the light, James
Do not row parallel to the light, you'll never get there
We were going towards it and then it sh
Oh
Is my wife here?
Did my wife row a boat?
She could never rowboat, her arms are too weak
She's a woman
James must suspect that his wife's not actually here, right?
Well, at this point, he's been through a lot of supernatural stuff that he is
That's true
completely disregarded, so
That's a good point
I think he's too in it, he's too lost in the sauce
Yeah, he just has to keep hoping that he can make amends, I guess
It's like, see, I was a good husband, I never gave up. -I followed through on my promise
to stand by your
No
Spend money
These waters will bring you peace!
Fifteen dollars for the day
Fifteen dollars to hold to hang? Pretty nice
Yeah, but how long realistically am I going to
be rowing around out there
Well, you can take it to go fishing
You could take it to Go Vision, count me out
I actually like fishing. -I like sitting on a boat. -I don't like the act of
herding of fish
No, I will sit on the boat, that's for sure
Yeah, yeah
Puddle
I like that you can see the building more clearly in the puddle than you can
That is interesting
Like there's someone there
Or is that a phone?
I think it's a... a false
Affonse
Falls! Falls!
Let's see if there's anything over here
Very well landscaped over here
It's beautiful, flowers are thriving
Well, it's very humid, so
That's true
Is there a way to make the achievement volume louder?
I feel like I wasn't notified clearly enough
I'd really like to crank that up if I could
I can still hear other things, so I feel like
I feel like we can make it louder
Oh, it's my flashlight. I thought I saw a little
Dude, put me right there in those two chairs, not those, left those. -That's me and you right there
Oh yeah, 100%
Absolutely chilling
and then we're like, oh, this is amazing, and then we put in an order for food, and then we start being slightly inconvenienced by bugs
Yeah, and then we're like, never mind, outside was a mistake
Wait, what?
No items
They got the
How does this chain work?
It's lots of different chains, OK?
No, it's like all linked together, is one chain
Cacao!
As the cold draws near, they abandon their old nests to return in time
Hmm
That's James right there
Oh
Rotten apple
I'm really glad that the
Sound effect half
Made like a squish
Yeah
I'm the rotten apple, it's me. Oh yeah, put that in your pocket
Do you
James, why are you keeping that, bro?
Because it's gross, he only deserves the grossest things, okay?
I was going to say you should throw that thing as hard as you can against a tree, it's really fun
Lone one of the east, out of the water safety now lost out of breath
Why'd you go out of the water? You're a fish
Lone one of the east
I can't loan the east, that's too big. -And I don't own it
This has got to be some Puzz shit
Yeah, oh yeah
This is some major puz
I hear peeing
Pianus
I hear it
I know there's another statue, I'm going to go towards the piano in the interest of
Welcome back
they knew I was here before
They've been waiting for you. Is that a leather jacket?
Sure is
It's like a
Buddy?
cool white leather jacket
Yeah
Is that Mary's jacket? She had a cool ass jacket
Uh, Mary was wearing... red
Well, yeah, she took off the jacket and left it here
Oh, yeah
Oh, waiting for you
That's my birthday
How'd she know?
She's your wife
That's how
Do you know what my birthday is, Jacob?
Do I know what your birthday is, the one you just said?
Yeah, do you know?
If I didn't know before, I definitely do now
Well, what is it then?
Oh shit, oh no
Oh my God, it's the same
No, I told you, I've got the perfect mnemonic device for your birthday
Okay, what is it?
March one two
Oh, okay, how'd you know?
I just
I'll never forget because it's like someone marching. -They're like, march, one, two, one, two
I'll never forget
Well, I super remembered your birthday after you pointed out that it's-- -That it's 69
That it's 6'9
Oh, the rotten apple didn't work here
Yeah, it's a hard one to forget
Look at this good ceiling
That is a good ceiling
Do you know that ceilings like that were originally in the Duomo and it was a way of making a domed ceiling that was lighter?
like lighter in weight
So that it wouldn't collapse under its own weight
Yeah
So they made this, they invented that kind of ceiling for that building
Well, let's investigate the piano
You ever noticed how if you say Duomo, it sounds like you're doing baby voice?
Yeah
Dwellmo
Do you want to go to the Duomo?
Yeah
I want to see the Duomo
I'm going to probably
OK, fine
Dwellmo
Do we think it's
Maria?
Hello?
I want you to know that if a cut scene started, I would stop talking
Well, I didn't want to cut you off
Intermezzo
Johanes Brahms
Grames
I had no good way to mispronounce Brahms, it's spelled exactly like it sounds
The Hames!
I said no good way to mispronounce it, oh
Someone disagrees with you
Laura?
Yeah
You did
Laura's like, James is like, oh God. -Someone else to trauma dump on me
Then again, maybe you're not so bad, just
Annoying. -That's fair
So
I think you've had enough... for now
Wow
That's reassuring
She's here
Isn't she?
Come on, tell me
I wish I knew
But
She said it in her letter
So there really is a letter
Oh
Yeah
Wanna read it?
Just
Don't tell Rachel, OK?
Just says fuck you in it
She's our nurse
I
I took it from her locker
I love you
All right
How old are you?
Last week
Yeah, I mean
James, think about it like a little harder
She even showed me all her pictures
She really wanted to come back
She also talks a lot about you, you know?
Seven
What?
What is it?
Well
It kind of was his other letter
I think the warmer's for you
Wanted to
This one time, I almost dead
You didn't deserve to have it
But then
Yeah
Just says I know what you did last summer
three years ago
three years ago, last, last, last summer
It's empty
Get rekt
Wait
Sit down
I gotta find it
Laura!
Well
I did love the person in chat who was saying,  James, honey, you jumped into your own grave and ended up outside of a lake house. Like think about it a little bit
Yeah, yeah, ads are going to start soon, so we might as well just like
But James is not experiencing things in a lucid state of mind. He's in like a psychedelic dream dimension
Yeah, yeah
I mean, it's like when you're having a dream, everything makes sense to you even though it's all nonsense
Yeah
That's kind of what James is experiencing
I'm going to run the ads
,OK, you don't want me to talk this stream, I get it
Ellie, you just have bad timing
Every time I start talking, you're like, -let's have you stop talking
I just said I was going to run the ad
And then you went on
Let's have you stop talking and then we can do something else
I said I was going to run the ads and then you just wouldn't shut the fuck up
I just thought we could have like a moment of conversation while we waited for the ads to start
I thought we could kind of digest what was happening in the game and the story for a second
No, I like it
Clearly you didn't like it
I just like
With these last streams of games, it's always like we can go a little long, so I'm just trying to like
play the game and do the yapping at the same time
Oh, I'm sorry, I thought we were enjoying ourselves on stream
Of being efficient
I thought we were having a nice time talking to each other in the chat
We keep getting comments that are like, this is not the optimal way to play the game
Today, optimal
Optimal, we're locking in
Optimal!
We're speed running the rest of this. -If you skip the cut scenes, it goes a lot faster actually
Oh, we might as well
Yeah
Just finish it
Somebody asked me to talk about the new Elden Ring
Who cares about the story?
I think it looks super sick, I'm really excited about it
it's pretty much just like
It looks like they're just like,  how can we take all this shit we made and then put it in a package that's just like maximum fun?
Yeah
get your friends together and let's fucking speed run Elden Ring
And
and fight bosses from like the whole Souls series
Yeah
I'm psyched about it. I think it's going to be a really good time
Yeah, as my mistake said,  hey, people modded our game, let's do it ourselves, actually, that's exactly what I said to Julia. I was like, clearly they looked at all of the top mods that everyone loved for Elden Ring and they were like, let's just take all the top mods and put all of them into one game
Yeah, that is
Yeah, the other thing that we were talking about, not to like
bring down the hype
Oh, here we go
She's going to tell me to stop talking again
but I really got to play this game, so I appreciate if you can lock the fuck in
No, um
It's that I love, so there's like a thing that happens on the internet and the internet's like a big place, so you're going to get a lot of
viewpoints and stuff like that, and then it's easy to cherry pick the worst ones and then say that's everyone. But we were laughing about the comments that were like, but my favorite part about Elden Ring isn't represented here, and it's like, so play Elden Ring
Play that part
Yeah, I was mainly going on a complaint rant to Julia about how there's a lot of people that watch YouTube game trailers and they seem to have no ability to extrapolate from what they saw in the trailer into what the game will be like. -And so I saw a lot of comments that were like,
Yeah
Well, what I love about the Souls games is the slow exploration of these areas and like slowly discovering things and playing by myself. But then they say, and I'm worried this new game is not going to have that. And I'm like, it's not going to have that. Did you watch the trailer?
So do I
Yeah, that's not what they're going for, dog
We don't have to guess if it's going to have it. It's literally just like, look at what you saw and tell what kind of game it is. Like, I don't know what you're talking about
Yeah
It's like
Yeah, I don't know
It's just like I understand where people are coming from, like I
,Well, like, I think that if you're a very particular kind of Zelda fan, and this is related, you like some of the games, but not the other games, and then if you're another kind of fan, you love, you know
the other games more than the first kind of games and it's like, but it's like kind of
They're playing around with it, you know? It's fun, it's a toy
,Something for everyone, what's on your nose?
And I wanted to draw attention also to the fact that
Can I get it off your nose?
I also saw people complaining about like asset reuse in the game
And the first thing I thought of was like, -you better not be one of those motherfuckers who's like, -Majora's Mask is my favorite game or Fallout New Vegas is my favorite game. -If you're then going to come in here and be like, they're reusing assets, I'll kill you
Yeah
Some of the best games ever made are from reused assets which freed up the devs to make some of their best and most exciting and interesting work
They have so much time to do other stuff. And they already made all these high quality assets, why would you not use them?
Yeah
Sorry, go ahead, James
Go ahead, James, get it
Is it Mary's theme?
Right?
Yeah
I like that, that's fun
This game's unrealistic because he didn't immediately play the rugrats theme
On piano, that's the one you play if you don't know how to play piano
Yeah
I'm
trying to remember the rubber ass theme
Dun dun dun dun dun dun, dun dun dun dun dun, dun dun dun dun dun, dun dun dun dun dun, dun dun dun dun dun
Oh
Yeah, yeah
Laura, it's cool, I don't deserve letters from my dead wife, it's okay. Also, I did like in chat, and this is not a call out because this game is very confusing and a lot of things are not literal, but someone was like, oh, Mary's actually dead, and I was like, yeah, yeah
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, no, she's dead for real
She been dead, she done been dead
She been dead
Oh, there's a save point
Don't mind if I do
but again, I completely understand why there's some confusion
,Mr. James Sunderland, regarding the videotape you left in your room during your last stay, ew, gross, icky,
Ewe, ewe, ewe, I watched it
Ew, ew, ew
Why did you leave that there?
Gross
I'm glad to inform you that we've recovered the item and moved it to the employee section on the first floor. The tape is stored within the hotel safe to be returned to you at your earliest convenience. Please pick it up
Now, I don't want it here anymore
I do not want it
Music books
There's the
You're 12
Someone said spoilers
Listen, we jumped into our own grave and wound up at a lake
Mary's dead
You go jump into your own grave and see what happens
Well, well, what the fuck?
Oh, you know
What the hell kind of contraption is this?
It's a music box, you dumbass
No, it isn't
Oh, and dusty
Give me this
Oh
,Mm
That's a staff only room
Oh, yeah, that's why I can't go home
102, we'll take that
Well, the hotel needs renovations anyway
Break on through to the other side
I like that they definitely wanted me to follow
Laura, and I was like,
time to look for items
What Laura doesn't realize is that we're gaming
Yeah, yeah
guitar
Go ahead
buckaroo
Remember that strange book you found earlier?
some very odd looking man came in a few hours back, claimed to belong to him. Honestly, I didn't feel like arguing
I'm not sure how he even knew it was here
I don't think he was ever a guest here, I would have remembered
I just can't get it out of my head. Girl, your eyeballs are all I think about
Get it out of my head.
On Ironically, a song
That gets stuck in my head
as probably designed
I thought you were just going to say  unironically a song. -I was going to be like, that is so true
Ironically, a song
Unironically, that is a song
Literally not even joking
Literally, he's a song
Laura?
Well
We don't have to be like this
The gurgler is here
Well, I gotta
key from 102
James, you're going to get gurgled, bro
James, you got gurgled, bro. I freaking warned you
I told you
James was told about the tape and he was like,
All I can think about are legs again
Yoink
Okay, 102
Is Laura a real person? You tell me
You tell me, buckaroo
It's like a vent
You tell me what you think
I want to hear your theories, chat
I know she's a video game character
Damn, though
Fuck, that's true
I was ready
I'll take that
We're kind of all video game characters if you think about it because the universe is a simulation
Yeah
I did mushrooms once, so I know that that's true
I did mushrooms once and it made me think about my size relative to the world because I've never thought about that independently before
Damn, we got the balcony view
I'm ready to shoot
Now this is a delightful spot
I will say though, if my balcony is like directly next to my neighbor's balcony and there's not a wall there, my ass is not going out there
Yeah
Because I'm at risk, I might have to talk to them
I'm at risk for forced socialization
So I'll do that
Why'd you... huh
What? Why are we hunting?
,Draz said,  ,Hmm, fanfic prompt. That's actually a good setup
Yeah
forced shared balcony
I actually read a manga like that
You could have the one character who's really like shy and introverted and doesn't want to socialize, but they accidentally lock themselves on the balcony and out comes the social butterfly talkative neighbor
Oh boy, odd couple situation
Yeah, I read one, it was a guy who used his outside
OK, outside balcony is like a little garden space and then his next door neighbor
Um
just like moved in or something. I read this a while ago, so I can't remember, but... ...then they started talking because of his beautiful garden space
Who's squelching out there?
Reveal yourself
Whenever somebody types WLW,
in describing a fic or manga or something, I always read it as
Oh!
And then there's of course, Mlem
Wooloo, wooloo
Do you read Mlem or
Which is your favorite?
Whoa!
Just fucking
standing there
All right, weirdo
home office romance, is that what it was called?
Wasn't one of them like an archaeologist who wanted to like travel or something?
It was cute
All right, you're about to bust into an interpretive dancer
You know when they start to fold it up and they're like,
Yeah
That's my impression of interpretive dance. That's my interpretation of interpretive dance
It's an interpretation of interpretation
That's meta interpretive dance, post interpretive dance
I was about to say, that's like an art movement
Fuck
F
I'm
Crafty
I'm ahead of the time. -I wasn't expecting to be able to open that
Us actually crisis?
I wanted to say to chat also, because somebody said they caught up on  Marianetta and they don't know what to read now. -I'm also caught up on Marianetta, except for like the, you know, paid chapters
It's so good, man. -But it reminded me there was a new comic that just started coming out on Webtoon that's really cute
Oh, is it the cozy one that you were... that I started reading?
It's the cozy one
It makes me think of like a comic version of like a Stardew Valley-esque scenario. -It's called Little Hollow Cafe
about a woman who moves to a small town to run a cafe and then meets all of the other people that work and live there
really cute art style. -It feels like a Stardew Valley game that you're reading
Yeah, yeah, it's really cute
It's on Webtoons, super cute so far, and it's just started, so
I want to talk about the environmental storytelling of this room
Yes
bottle, a bunch of like blood stains, just cigarettes like literally everywhere. It's great
um, the damp carpet, like the worn carpet with like the footprints that I didn't leave
more staining over here from this bottle. Like, look at... there's more cigarettes over there
There's this
There's that, um
I love the fingerprints in the dust
more cigarettes, blood or wine or something like
someone down in this room and it wasn't good
No
There's like alcohol everywhere, there's a vase on the floor
The carpet's all moldy
You don't want to be in this room. -You don't want to be around the person who was in this room
No
That's how I enter the bathroom every time I have to pee
That's apparently how I entered the bathroom when I dislocated my knee
because I thought I entered it normally, but
You know?
You think you enter a room normally and then your knee is somewhere else?
That'll happen sometimes
That'll happen
This is extremely narrowcasting to Marionetta readers, but PeachyLove asked me Team Sahed or Tani
,And you don't even have to ask that question to me, you know I'm Team Sahed
He's too hot
He's too hot to be ignored and he's unhinged
Those legs were just walking around
And I like followed them and killed them
What's-what happens?
Oh, speaking of which, I
I got in Dragon Age, I just got Tosh
It was very fun
Daniel Tosh?
from Tosh.0
Uh-huh
It's a crazy twist in the game. -Daniel Tosh shows up and you're like, -I don't want to play this game anymore
Are you going to be here the whole time?
Suddenly I find this game irritating
Sorry, please continue talking about Tosh
Daniel Tosh?
Sun room!
Anyway, Tasha's great
Hedera Helix seems to have some kind of pest separate from the rest of the plants
Oh, separate
separate from the rest and plants are little die out
I read it the same way in your defense
OK, thank you
What?
What's the point of this room?
Bullets! That's the point of this room
Um, yeah, Tash is fun. I think my favorites right now though are
Um... Lucanus?
and Nev
But Tosh is up there
I don't love Emmerich
He's fine
He's fun. I like... actually, my favorite companions are Manfred and Asan
And they're not even companions
No, those are my favorite characters though
Someone said incredibly loud, incorrect buzzer. -Yeah, I feel like my Emmerich opinions are
Unwelcome, and I accept that
You misread, that person said incredibly correct buzzer
Oh, well, I accept that too
They were giving you a supportive buzzer
Thank you, thank you, thank you, I appreciate that
When did this get here?
Has this been here?
I think it's been there
Really?
Whoops
Okay
What do we have? We have keys for like a sunroom
Manfred is voiced by Matthew Mercer
Really?
He just goes,
Did they pay Matthew Mercer to go?
Did they pay him to
to just make noises. How much did they pay him his usual cut?
to just like squelch into a mic
They should have paid Julia to do that
I love to make those noises, it's so funny
Employee section, oh
We didn't do the employee section, right?
Oh, no, because I can't go in
Yeah, it's employees only, like
Can we go through the restaurant?
Sorry, are you an employee?
You're right
punched that door open
Oh
Okay, no
No, it would be through there. Okay
All right, that's fine, whatever
Frickin... what?
Man
Somebody said they paid Vin Diesel to say I am Groot
That's true, but he said it in a lot of different ways
And I don't know, I'm pretty sure they didn't use him for Marvel Rivals, -but whoever they use is getting a lot of screen time. -Because I am Groot fucking... -If Groot's on your team, that's all you hear the whole game. -He won't shut the fuck up about how he's Groot
Yeah, I wish you would chill
to be fair, freaking Tandy's like,
It's so cold
Cloak and dagger is still my favorite to play
I do laugh at everything Tandy says, though
Tease!
Tandy?
Cloak is fun, but... Whoa, I need to look at that painting
Well, that seems a little on the right
Pride before the fall, huh?
Just seems a little
Seems a little on the
And did you notice that Leonard E. Niavos is an anagram for James Sunderland?
if you rearrange all the letters and change some of them to different letters
Did you notice that stalwart to the end is actually James Sunderland if you rearrange all of the letters?
And then change some of the letters. -I did notice that actually
And then change some of the letters
It's pretty crazy
Did you notice that if you change
Bottom Hat said,  it does make me laugh every time I hear Luna Snow say I suck
I suck
That is what we hear every time too  and we laugh at it. -I think she's saying like iced up or ice up, but it sounds like she's screaming
Yeah
I suck
It cracks me up
We need to talk about this painting
AI generated, I can tell
I just... the eagle just hanging out there
Truly, America has like ruined American Bald Eagles for me because every time they're in there, I'm like,
America, America
Because it is your turn, yeah
Oh, man, Jacob and I were listening to
Oh my god, is her name Samara? Samara Joy?
Is that her name?
Yeah
What? Oh
So we were listening to her album, her like
She's a jazz singer
She's a jazz singer, great
What was I talking about? I got distracted by it because I thought I was just going to twist the little middle thing and then it was like, which book do you want to use?
anyway, she's great
Um
You had something you were connecting to
What was I connecting it to?
We were singing America the Beautiful in like a Creed voice
I lost it, I lost it
Instead, you just said that a singer was really good, which is also acceptable
I mean, she's great
Okay
I feel like you need a fourth buck
Oh, that's what it was. So I went on a really quick brain tangent. So the way that Jacob sung the end of that song where basically none of the words were intelligible reminded me of that
Christmas song about that one woman song where it was like,
Quizmoys
Yes
Like quiz-moss or whatever she says, is that Christmas?
Or whatever she said,  it said Christmas. We need more info though. Which song was it?
Cause I'm trying to remember
I literally only have the Kelly Clarkson Christmas song stuck in my head, which is not it. -Quizmice, thank you. Camilla Cabello, sorry. Quizmoice
Yes, yes, okay, thank you for knowing because I also couldn't fully get there either. I was like, I know what you're talking about, and I want to provide the proper context, but I can't get it. I'll be home for Christmas, thank you. Oh my God
Thank you
Good lord, thank you for catching it
Yes
I'll be home for
Wiz-mice
Um, and if you listen to Samara Joy's Christmas album, it's so freaking good
And in the middle of it, I was like,  do you think she thought about saying Quizmoize?
Where's Moise?
All right, I don't know which book goes where, I also don't have all the books
No, you're missing a book
Oh
I like how you were like,  Jacob, let's get through the game quickly. And then you're like, let me stop and stare at a bookshelf for five full minutes while I try to remember Camila Cabello
Doesn't work today Jacob, I'm struggling. Mine doesn't either. That's why I need you to lock in so that one of us can be locked in!
One of us has to be locked in!
I can't be locked in, I'm stupid today!
We have to both lock in so we get like half a brain
It's locked out
of our own minds
Pride Before the Fall, that's Alliance, that's top left, and then Eagle
Oh, freaking pride
Quizmo
Quizmoiz
Um
The one who's sword, that's the freaking eagle
That's a eagle
Is that an eagle?
Whatever
That's a ongle
And that's a devil
Now hit the thing in the middle
You can't
I
You did it wrong
How did I do it wrong?
Lion?
Bull?
Eagle, angel
Eagle angle
Does it have to be
flipped to mirror the thing?
Is this not... wait
Wait, okay, hold on, the spears, the spears mean something. Oh, we got to go upside down
The spears are upside down
,Lion, eagle, no
Yes
Yeah, yeah
And backwards, upside down and backwards
Wait, and backwards, and backwards, and backwards. -We got there, ladies and gents
Yikes!
All right, I'm locking in, I'm locking in, Jacob
She's so locked
Oh, a six spot
She's locked and stocked
And she got two smoking barrels
I've never seen that movie
neither have I, but I imagine that that's what it's about. It's about a few people trying to focus on a video game together
I think so
Yeah
The gray adder said,  OMG, it's actually James, I wish I was a fan
That would be such a fucked up thing to say to someone
Help
Oh, is it Mary?
Miffy
Milp, milp
Mouth, Mouth
Mewi
It wasn't help Mary
Put Milf Mary
Okay, yeah, hold on, let me
It's going to be Milfmerry
Okay, hold on
Oh, it's going to be  Milk Mary, Milk Mary
No, it can't be, Jacob. -It can't be, it can't, we can't. -We can't, we can't!
It's got to be a milk Mary
Can't!
Oh my God!
Oh, there's a lot of blood under that door
Next to your list stream, we're doing a Milk Mary kill
What'd you do to the light bulb?
You know
Stuff happened
How you get blood on the light bulb?
But apple didn't work
I don't know, someone probably got pushed into it. -Didn't you ever see that clip from Whose Line is it Anyway?
Where Ryan Stiles smashed his head into a light bulb
but like for fake
No, no, he did it by accident
Was he okay?
He was okay, he just had a lot of glass in his head
Oh no
It was very funny, he was someone who keeps getting magnetized to things and he like went to go get stuck to Drew Carey's desk
And
And he headbutted the lights that were on his desk and
Hello?
We have
Okay, the only one we have is
Hello? Oh
He had a lot of glass in him, it was very funny, Julia LePetit 2024
My brother, when we were kids,
or when I was a kid, he was like in high school or something
That's also a kid
Yeah, yeah
If you think about it
Yeah, he was in the
Why is there like a frog?
Um
Do you
Anyway, he got into a car accident where he went through the windshield
because he wasn't wearing a seatbelt, and then we had to go to
uh, like a mass, basically, it was like for my confirmation or whatever
And during the mass, I was picking glass out of his head and we like, my mom asked us how it went and we were like, oh, it's pretty fun. -I just picked glass out of Mike's head for the entire thing and she was like, what?
Wait, what? How much time was in between these two things happening?
Oh, like a day. He was in the hospital for like a few days or something
They didn't take the glass out of his head in the hospital?
He had some leftover
It was really stuck in there, he went through the windshield of his tree
I remember that story
Yeah
Anyway, wear your seatbelt, everyone
They were just going like down the block
Do you have any more horrifying stories you want to tell about people getting glass embedded in their heads?
No, that's all of it
Nice dodge
Thank you
Um
My brother and all of his friends, by the way, were sober. His friend just like unfortunately hit a curve
A curb
And
the car did not behave itself
Okay
Okay, we came back around
When I come around
What the hell was that?
That was me saying when I come around
There's some thunking and muttering
and like someone was saying something
Yeah, that was the muttering I was referring to
Because I think that's
No, it's two
That's a
Okay
I knew it!
Jerk
I got you
You know they thought they had you too. -They were like, I'm going to get his ass
Yeah
Do I? Ha ha!
That kind of sucks
It's probably a cheaper room
Well, I mean like the wallpaper's fallen
Oh yeah, you're right
If I ran a hotel, I would keep like a couple rooms that were like intentionally like incredibly shitty that I could give to people for really cheap
But I would make them like shittier on purpose
They'd be in fine condition when you got to them
Yeah
I think that's what poor people deserve, really
That's what I'm kind of getting at here
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I think you're right
No
I saw you, okay
I want to call you out
Oh, we've been in this room
Yeah, we've been here, this is the Swan room
I'm trying to remember what my friend Kevin said when we were in Georgia where he was like,
All you need is a good nest egg
He was like, why is anyone poor? All you need is a good nest egg and substantial cash flow
Yeah, that is what he said. That's exactly what he said
He was like, it's so easy, it's two steps. -Just have a good nest egg and then a substantial cash flow
Yeah
it cracked me up
He was not serious in case that was unclear. -But he delivers everything like he is serious
No
But his delivery every time
It's so dry
Yeah
Why are we so choppy?
What's up with this room?
We gotta get out of the shopping room
is happening
Oh, that's what I was doing wrong
Yeah, if you don't have
a big enough nest egg, just save more money until it's big enough. -And if you don't have enough cash flow, then just make more money
so that more cash is coming in
Yeah
And then you'll have both of the things in the two-step process
They forgot the bed
They forgot the bed in this one
Everyone in chat is like,  I feel so stupid right now
Yeah, you should
Yeah, like why didn't you do it?
Why is it so simple? Why didn't you just do that?
What the hell is a nest egg? -'See, this is why you're struggling
If you don't know what a nest egg is,
Sorry, you just don't have it
Kevin is genuinely so funny
He sounds so serious
Kevin is one of my best friends since like
elementary school
He, um
Can we help you?
Come here, Miss Odin! At the wedding that we were in, or that we went to, Kevin was in it, and he kept rummaging in his pocket and locking eyes with me and going, you want some? You want some of this? You want this? You want some? You want to partake? You want some? You want this? Like that rapidly, and I was like, what are you talking about? And then he finally got it out of his jacket after like two minutes of trying to get this thing out of his blazer. It was a freaking wedding ring,
And then he just kept saying,  you want some of this?
You want some?
You want some of this?
And then you just kept saying, yeah, take it
And then Jacob's other friend, who I'd only met once
Um
We said hi to him
We're like, oh, hey, haven't seen you in a while. He's like, oh yeah, I'm a yo-yo
He's just starting yo-yoing. -He's like, uh, kind of sucks
Yeah, my friend Key
I was like, what is happening?
Okay
I'm pretty sure I was like, I saw him, he was dressed really nicely. -I was like, I was like, damn dude, you look really good. -And he was like, oh, thanks, I got a yo-yo
Yeah, yeah, he did do that
And just pulled a yo-yo out of his jacket and started yo-yoing
Good times. -That was a really baffling series of events at this wedding for me
Do I have normal friends? No
Uh-uh
But all the ones I do have are ride or die, lifelong
I would say you have one group that is very normal
Which group? College Friends?
Yeah
College friends are probably the most normal
Now I get why Jacob is funny, he was raised in the funny. -It's literally one of those things that I think all the time is that,
I feel like all of my friends are funnier than I am
And so I'm oftentimes
confused and baffled by the fact that I've managed to make a career out of
it to some degree
Because in my mind, I'm like, but I'm not as funny as like any of my friends
Right
I'm like
any of them should be more successful than me, but none of them tried to do it, so
But I do think
That's their mistake
I do think that being a funny person and making that a transferable skill,
like an accessible skill, like your friends are funny
but I got better social skills
Yeah, like, like Kevin
I'm well balanced, I'm like Mario
Kevin cracks me up, but it's truly only because we've played video games with him enough
that I've gotten used to the things that he says being jokes
because half of the time I'm like,
I don't know if you're serious or not
Yeah, I guess that is true. Most people, when they meet him, do not know what to make of him
I am often very confused
Do you have a comedy nest egg and substantial funny flow? I do, yeah, my funny flow is off the charts. I'm getting all the funny from my friends
That's where the funny flow comes in  and then I save it in my comedy nest egg
So how do we get up?
But there's something about people who I think are like the funniest people and it's that they're not just like
,people who are being funny, it's that the funny is like a part of them. -It is like how they live their life
Yeah
something in like their very nature is funny
And there's like, you can't manufacture that kind of funny. -You either are that person or you're not that person
Hmm
I have to like think
a lot about it
Right
And then, you know, be funny. -They're just like, they just are funny. -I think that's the difference
That's how I am with dourness
born into the dourness
like I find you... we have a friend, the other friend that we play
Marvel with
,uh, along with Kevin
who I also think is very funny, but he's like
a really inaccessible funny
He's like an insult comic
He is like an insult comic, like it cracks me up and you just have to be like ready for it
So... okay
They said the thing was in the safe in the employee area, so it's not here, right?
I didn't unlock this while I was here earlier
I wasn't locked in yet
but I'm locked in now
Um
Like, I would say that his comedy only works with a very particular group of people
Yeah
But I do find him very funny
I mean, I do too, that's why we've been friends for so long
Yeah
We did that. The vanity mirror, we don't have the light bulb for
202 we don't have the key for. I probably missed something in one of these rooms, huh?
You know what? Is it
was I supposed to know the lock combo?
Milk Mary
Yeah
Was I supposed to know that?
Not yet, people are saying
Okay
breakable wall on the second floor
Second floor, okay, thank you
Gift shop maybe?
Like I said, my brain just engaged
You can jump the counter in the cloak room on the second floor
That explains the white, I was wondering about that, and for some reason I just didn't try it, but thank you
Wow
What is happening in this room?
I quit
Why would you do that?
How could this happen to me?
That's... I don't like any of this. Look at the legs
The legs are really cracking me up
That's like your drunk Aunt Linda
who stumbled over the couch
Oh, 202
That was a totally random name and I realize now you do have an album
I do have an Aunt Linda who does not drink
No, but I think in general, if you took a survey,
of all the Aunt Lindas in America
I think more than 50% of them would be the type to drink too much and fall over the couch
That's fair
That's what I would guess
Okay
An un-rotten apple
A ripe epazote
Ripe apple
Who put that there?
Right back, boo
I'll be right back
Hello, sir
Looks like my friend Kyle
Weird
Bullets on the balcony
We love to see it
Take no prisoners
I heard the noises she was making and I went,  mm-mm
We're not doing it
Not doing it
MSS, Mary Sunderland
Stacy Sunderland
Mary Stacy Sunderland
Oh, you can't open it?
I can't open it, apparently. James is not interested
James wants nothing to do with it. -Is there anything in there? Nope, is there anything in here?
Nope, all right, I just broke this for nothing, that's fine, it was satisfying
What about these? Anything? No? What about this?
Anything?
No, okay
Someone
Someone in one of the YouTube VODs, like, time stamped one of the nurses and it says,
And they wrote like, why did she make that noise? Oh my God, was that a mistake?
Are we missing the point?
I think we know why
Are we missing the point of these?
I think we know why she made the noise
of these non-literal ladies?
Like a Dark Souls character taking a hit
Yeah
Not of weed
Well, they could be
Maybe
If your Dark Souls protag took a big puff and was like,
Oh
No prisoners
I suffer no fools
Okay
What do you think they're burning on those bonfires? -So true, I think they're sitting at the bonfire so much
anything in this cabinet?
Buh
Bottles
Take a jizzle of the scoobert, Ashen1
Don't remind me of shit I said
Smell of Vader, smell of Vader, taste
Okay
Just going to check all these rooms
Oh!
You can't go back to your hiding spot, all right?
No, we know
But blow it, you can't reset, okay? I'm sorry
You get one hit for a good measure
One hit
We see you
Damn, you never stood a chance
No, well, she stood
but not a chance
Not a chance
I came to this hotel with my porcelain and my box and the porcelain didn't survive
All that was in the suitcase was one loose porcelain doll and a wooden box
Damn, damn, damn
It's a great shame
Great shape
Okay, you didn't get to find anything in one of those?
Oh
I do want to say I appreciate the
Don't
I appreciate the level of backseating that's been happening during this Silent Hill game, and I don't know if it's chat being real good with their backseating, which I appreciate, or if it's the mods, but I feel like everyone's letting me make mistakes, and then when I'm genuinely confused, someone throws me a little hint
Chat's been good, they've been good for this game
They were great
Very proud of you, Chad
Chat, you've made me proud, puts my hand on your shoulder in a fatherly gesture since I'm going to be a father now
That's true
I'm going to be saying so much dadly shit to y'all
Mm-hmm
I'm gonna be like doling out advice
I am, but yeah, it's been really nice because my goal with Secret Sleepover,
is to enjoy the game how it's meant to be enjoyed. Shall I use a rotten apple? No
the Puss in the Doll though, but also, you know, not to get too bogged down. So when people like jump on me to play the game optimally, I'm like, okay, let's chill. But
Since it's taking you this long to get to the conference room,
You might as well drop by room 107, I'm leaving you the key, one of the guests made quite a mess
Ooh, a little Messi Milton in 107
I'll take that one kill
A bit of a messy Melissa
Eww
I found the problem, Silent Hill, it's black mold everywhere
That's like always the answer
It's always the answer
If you have any problem in your life, you should really check your living space for black mold
Roll that one out first
Yeah, get one of those mold sniffing dogs in your house
Jacob and I were watching something and there was this girl with like a metric ton of problems and she was like seven
like a ton of health issues and depression and
A ton of health issues
anxiety and panic attacks and couldn't go out anywhere and just like issue after issue after issue and they were like, suddenly it just hit like out of nowhere and then they looked at a room and it was just like full of black mold
Yeah, the walls were like
peeling off with black more like
The walls are like more black mold than wall
Mary?
Hello?
May we?
Dodge, Julia, dodge. You can't stun him, there's no stunning in this game
They're always going to hit you if they're in there
jump scare animation
Yeah
You do have approximately 50 healing items, that's not an exaggeration
Yeah, it's true
May we? Well, she's in 312 or whatever, right?
Yeah, we got to go to 107
,107.5, the room
Well, we have the key to 312
We have the key to 107
That's true. Should we go to 107 first or should we just try 312?
Do whatever you want, man
See if I care
That's 318
Yeah, I was just trying them since we're over here anyway
Who's that? Oh, it's Joy Cat
It's Joy Cat, it's Joy Cat
She is a beautiful cat
Joy, the laugh is, oh, she gave you a headbutt
Really strong one
Make a space for her immediately
Come here
There she is, there she is
Hi
We've been giving... so the cats have
a massive lump on their throat, which is very worrying, but we're trying some antibiotics first
and some like anti-inflammatory stuff and whatever
because it's in like a tricky spot, so we don't want to like, you know, do a biopsy, we're trying to see if it goes away
Since giving her the medicine, hello, she's back to her old self
of being kind of an asshole
Yeah, so I think we may have found an issue
Yeah, she's like a little bit of a rascal
But yes, both cats, we were at the vet and the vet was like, we told the vet that Joy had a lump on her neck and he was like, oh, that's really concerning. -He was like, I'm not sure what it is, we'll try this, we'll try this. -And then we're like, also Olive has a lump on her neck in the same spot
What?
Hey
And then he felt and he was like, what the?
That's really confusing, why would they
Yeah
Both?
Our vet is also like extremely good
Uh
He looks so puzzled for the rest of the visit
He was like, it's really bothering me
He would pause and just be thinking
Yeah
We really, really, really like our vet. He was a... he worked at like
you know, cat rescues for the longest time
Um, so he knows his stuff, so when he says something's puzzling, I'm like, uh-oh
That ain't good
I do feel like their throat's getting better though
But I
Yeah, I mean, they've both been acting
better, I do think it might be a... they both got like really bad colds
Yeah
and were like sick for a while and then after that this happened
And so I don't know if it was like some sort of little like infection from being sick and coughing
or like an irritation in the lymph nodes or
Yeah
Someone said maybe it's a lymph node, so the lump is not like
It's like a little too low
Yeah, it's too low on the neck to be a lymph node, but we thought the same thing, and then when we told our vet, he thought the same thing, and then he felt it, and he was like, it's not a lymph node. He's like, I also don't like how it feels
So
But Joy does, like we said, seem to be
feeling a lot better since we started giving him the medicine, so
Absolutely, she's
When I say she's like kind of an asshole, she's still the sweetest cat, but she is getting into trouble
She's trying to steal fish from Jacob
Yeah
She's jumping in the cabinets.  When I open a cabinet, she leaps in it. -She's going places she's not supposed to
Mm-hmm, she's a rascal
Not just half, and while you're at it,
Be sure to sweep up the leaves out in the garden, then you can get back to the fireplace, all right, jerk?
What? What? What? What?
What? What?
What? Is it the bug?
Well, they come
Here they come
Bang!
James, that felt like murder
It did, I did shoot her in the back
That one felt like she was just walking in the garden and you blasted her
Yeah, she was
That's what I'm talking about
The dodgies
I heard someone else
Uh-oh, there's dramatic music happening
I'm locked in, man, I woke up
for the first time today, I finally woke up
Are they drinking filtered water or tap? -They mostly drink tap water
Oh, yeah
Is there a thing with tap water and cats?
I have six lives
So something with everything
We change it every day though
The water fresh, it's NYC tap, yeah
It's a NYC tap
NYC tap, best tap water in the world
Incredible tap water over here
The bagel water, that's right, Draz
There's that bagel water
We're giving the cats bagel water
Pizza grade water
Yeah!
Someone mentioned thyroid issues, did they check that?
I don't think they checked that, but I don't know
I imagine that the vet will
I'm sure I'm bad when it's out of it
The vet would know
We have to go back the day after Christmas
Yeah
sorry, quiz mice
Quez-mais
And hopefully they'll be doing better by then and we'll have to do nothing more
Well, one
Joy's side, I was just trying to feel for it and I couldn't feel it
I think they're getting better
So do I
Speaking of tap water, and I'm not saying this about the tap water thing, it just like made me think of it
Here she goes
I'm about to say the most
I don't know, boomer thing I'm maybe ever going to say
Here it comes, she's booming
I think that if you go on
,uh, TikTok or social media
Uh oh
Here it comes
and you give... again, this is not about the tap water,
It just reminded me
You give bad information, health information, like medicine information, -and it's like purposefully misleading or incorrect or harmful, you should be fined
Straight to jail
stop selling your goddamn supplements and telling people to
sun their buttholes or whatever
Ads are about to start, so
I'm just so tired of it. I'm tired of like... So again, in my pregnancy, everyone has something to tell me
And all my friends who have something to tell me, it's been great. -It's like a village has come together, it's been so
heartwarming and sweet and like the nicest thing
Um, but like
the advice that they're giving me tells me that they weren't getting this advice, and that they were getting the opposite advice, and I was like
Who's giving you this bad advice?
Where are your friends getting their information from?
And a lot of it is like, oh, I saw a TikTok and then I just said it like it was a fact to other people and then they go around saying it's a fact and it's like,
No
Stop drinking like liquid metal or whatever. What are you doing?
I'm just like so tired of it
I'm going to go on TikTok, I'm going to start a series where I just like come on the screen and I'm like, don't let your baby look at the color purple
It will make them
Um
Eating disorder
You just literally pulled things out of a hat. Don't let your baby
Look at the color purple
But if you buy my peanuts,
What's this?
It fix it, it fix it. Buy my peanuts, it fix it
Yeah
So there's two things there. One, did you see the woman on TikTok who said that the reason that people have glasses is because they're using glasses?
Yeah, I see that's a classic one
It's great
That glasses are making your vision worse
Yeah, and that actually not wearing your glasses anymore will make your eyes stronger, so it's actually like a big con by glasses
Companies
Yeah, you got to train your eyes back up. -They're getting weaker because you're giving in to them
Yeah, it's
stupid, but it's like that's that's like exactly the kind of thing that people like say
and then they'll just do it
but only if you also sell supplements. My favorite argument is when they're like,
don't listen to your doctor, your doctor is bought by big pharma and they're pushing drugs on you and actually they get a commission every time they prescribe you a drug, you should instead use supplements and coincidentally I sell some, link in the description
Let's not think about that too deeply
Subscribe to my course
Yeah
If you take my course, by the end of it, you'll have 4020 vision
Yeah, she was selling that course
You'll be seeing it in the damn future
About eye exercises or whatever
Although, did you see that study that's like, your baby needs to have interactions with colors, it like helps their brain develop?
But not purple
What? Did you not see my TikTok?
Oh, I'm so sorry, I missed, I must've missed that. But there was that like sad beige mom movement where they were like coloring all their kids toys to not be neon colors anymore because they found it overstimulating and they didn't want to have to look at brightly colored kids toys anymore
or it was just like aesthetically pleasing or whatever the excuse was and then doctors were like,
Your kid needs that. Like they need colors, this is the reason that they're also brightly colored
The Sad Beige Babies. -Something really funny about that to me. -Great band name
You're so right, dude
The sad beige babies
Santa bitch, baby
All right
Anyway, yeah, hi, what's up? What's up, sweetie?
Joy, you got all your food
Olive's rising, she's rising, everyone please stand, please rise for Miss Olive
Yeah, there's a lot of like bad
information out there though for moms and a lot of like pressure about stupid things where it's like
I don't know, I'm so like
you know, let's just do our best with what we got at all times. Oh, wait, I got the bulk cutters. That's for outside, right?
I'm so just like, let's do the best with the information we got and let's just try to be as informed as we got, you know, all the time, like that's my goal and it's like, sorry, I was doing the best with what I had available and you know, I'll always be ready to fix or correct
Oh, it dissolved it
Um
If something new presents itself, I'm always open to like changing my mindset about a thing
)
Um
,Large one in the west, tempted by the Lord's appeal, failed to resist it
Oh, damn, it us though
Damn, so true
Joy, come here
Come here
The lore was how horny we felt
Everyone please rise
Joy is here
Joy Cat has arrived on the scene
Please salute your new president, Joy
I would gladly vote for Joy over our impending option
Olive has abdicated the throne
And joy has risen to the occasion
fireplace, okay, we got to, well, we went to 202, right?
We did go to 202, right? Well, we have to do the light bulb anyway
Uh, my little buddy
Reading room
Okay, yeah
Um
Anyway, like
There's so much pressure on moms to like do... to like get the best for their baby or they failed
which is like pretty classist, really
Um
Apple?
Why did James grunt?
You thought the light bulb went in the light bulb slot, you absolute dickhead
The hell?
Uh, okay
I guess we got to like, we probably got to like paint it red or something
Um
Anyway, one of the many things that
women are pressured about is like breastfeeding
because it is like better for your baby, I guess, but like they're like, don't use formula. If you use formula, you're up
failure
And that's like what someone was telling me is like how they were made to feel
about it, and they had some problems and they couldn't breastfeed and they had to use formula and it was like
What are you... what? Like what are you supposed to do? Okay, die, I guess. Like what?
Everyone in chat is saying fed is best and that's right. -You just want them to be fed
Yeah
like, okay, you tried this thing, it didn't work,
We gotta go to option B, it's not like... I don't
I'll tell you right now, Chad, the only breastfeeding I care about for my child is chicken breast and rice and broccoli and hitting the goddamn iron
temple and lifting and getting huge. That's all I care about
That's the only thing our child's going to be allowed to eat
they're going to be jacked
From day one, day one
And then we're going to make them an influencer over it, you know? -We're going to be like, this child is so strong
James?
You fucking dropped it
God damn it
Oh
Sup, motherfucker?
I'm obsessed. I'm obsessed with everything that just happened
That was the most relatable  James has ever been to me
Yeah
Okay
It's one of the freaking Legulas
Can I fight this thing or do I have to run? No, I probably gotta fight, huh?
No, that's not the weapon I wanted
That's not the weapon I wanted
Now that's the weapon I wanted
You need to shoot its ceiling hands
Oh, probably
Well
It feels like you should, right?
Yeah
Oh, yeah
Oh
The music's still playing, so I'm
Did you get it?
I think you got it
I think we're good, I think we're clear
Let's take a look
Take a look
It's in a book
Oh, look at them toes
They're all curled
Oh, got a lot of blood. Was that me? Did I do that?
And then the mouth, head and mouth hands
Oh
What could it mean?
Boy, James
In that shape, what could it mean?
James, we got to talk about how you view women
It's not
It's not great, man. -It's like certainly not good
It's not good, it's just not good
Yeah
Although this angle is very funny
I want them to sing in like three-part harmony. -Be like, hello, hello, hello
What about like the rhythm having like the, oh
Together now
Yeah
Um
You think he's gonna go home and be like,
Listen, this thing had a mouth
It's so powerful
It could suck onto the ceiling, am I right?
Hey, fellas
Had to get all the boys together to tell you about this thing I saw
Was I in a nightmare or a dream? Hey. -Hey, I couldn't even tell
Hey, I couldn't even tell
I got a lot of trauma, boys
Boys, I'm struggling
Boys, I'm going through it
I'm not going to talk about it though, I don't want to
Well
Something happened in this room
James is like, three mouths, talk about the perfect woman. -...and his friends are like, James, why are you weeping?
He's like, what are you talking about? -... None of them would say my name
Oh, I found it
say my name, say my name
I love you
Well, fuck me then, I guess, whatever
God
three mouths and none of them spoke, you know what I mean? I wish you would forgive me
Because I'll never forgive myself, boys, I'll tell you that much
You have to put that on
Brods, huh?
Ah!
All right, so we got the doll
Where'd that go?
I can just leave, all right, that's nice
Easy
Let's go
Get the frick out
All right, we're here
We were not here before
We don't have to behave this way
The bird room
Cage... bird cage room
What could it mean?
Hmm, yes
I hear a bird in one of them
Yes
Colonel
Wait, hold on
Why am I hearing birds but not seeing birds?
It's theater of the mind
Holy
Okay
Well, bird, if you're here, I can't free you because I cannot see you. Am I boring you?
Oh
Yeah
Could you like play more exciting style?
What about this?
Now we're getting somewhere
I need that book, hey!
Well, I gotta go underneath and then shoot it
Is that right?
Where is it?
There's a question mark
?At the restaurant?
What if you shoot it from here? Will it fall down there?
Shit
Save yourself the trouble
Jacob, you're a genius
Easy mode
You were just so excited to get a bunch of glass in your face
Listen, it's the theme of the day
You're like, it would be so funny
Ooh, more blood
Okay, I'm going to suspect
All right, they're probably behind this breakable wall
Probably
Oh, wait, is there anything in this?
Little something for James, little treat for James
Apparently not, okay
Come on, show yourself
Show yourself
They're not going to do it, Julia
You know they're
Squirmer
James, why'd you put your gun out?
The squirmler
Just kind of went, ah, and closed the door
Oh, thanks
That was pretty good
Don't mind me
Good measure?
Uh
What we got?
Yep, cannot be opened by hand
I see, that's why I couldn't
Hi, buddy
Can you open it by foot?
?That's a good question. Oh, we should go get that book, I guess
Let's go get it
It's one floor down, right?
Go to De Blanc
Yep
sing
? Go to the boat. ,
Oh, I went the wrong way
I'm just going to make sure. I think it's the restaurant
Whatever, I'll go
Stupid restaurant
Oh, I'm sorry, Joy, was my laugh not good enough for you anymore?
You got places to be, you got things to do
I need the ants, man
You want to sniff Julia's headphones?
Yeah
There it is
Oh, you got too hot, huh?
Make some space for you there
Oh, I thought she was moving it
I'm making space
holding space?
Okay
Can open
Great, you opened that like a freaking psycho
That's how I had to open that can of beans that one time when our can opener broke
Yeah, that's true
I just had to take a knife to the can of beans
Yeah, yeah, you did
I felt truly alive in that moment
Yeah
Resourceful
That's what you were. That's upstairs, right?
Yeah, OK
Any of y'all ever opened a can of beans with a chef's knife chat?
It's pretty exciting
It's pretty exciting stuff
No
No, yes, yes, hell yeah
Oh, job's done
Day done
Job's done. Oh, is that what the words are? All right
It's not Milk-a-Mary
D
Bead
Deed done
It's my favorite anime, D-D-Dun
deed-de-done
keep workshopping it, I think you'll get there
dee-da-dun
All right, I'm gonna save
I'll miss James's little blank face staring at me
You can boot the game up and look at it anytime
It won't be the same
Oh
Well, don't I feel silly?
Well, well, well
James, you found yourself in the employees chambers
What will you do?
!Ah!
What happened?
What's up?
That you got hurt
No, I have been sitting in a one way for so long that when I adjusted, I had to scream
I have to leave all my stuff behind
Oh
I've been stripped. Bear!
A one person elevator, huh?
What is this, a Parisian elevator?
Good thing you are one person
This ain't good. This ain't good for James
I don't even have a map?
Okay
No, Mappa's the studio that did Jujutsu Kaisen
You're so right, though
I'm making the Julia jokes tonight
I like it
I can tell
Sorry, I'm stressed, I'm being pursued
Oh, look at this
Oh, isn't this lovely?
Isn't this lovely?
Hey, what's everyone's least favorite Christmas song?
simply having a wonderful Christmas time
I was going to say, mine is simply having a wonderful Christmas time
One of the worst songs I've ever heard in my entire life
sing together
It's like he was forced to make the song
and he did it out of resentment
The chorus literally sounds like it's a record that's like skipping
Yeah
My favorite line of that is when he does the second verse and he's already established sort of like the rhythm of the song, and then he goes, oh, that's enough
He just like skips a line and just like kind of groans and goes, that's enough
Simply, happily
One of the Christmas songs, simply
having a wonderful Christmas simply
the fire of angel bliss
I don't know what I just interacted with because I can't see
Ding dong! Like, ding dong sounds so sarcastic
It's like he wrote it and he was hungover and he was like, the freaking church bells, I'm going to lose my mind
Oh
Nice
Santa baby's pretty rough too, for me
Oh yeah, I also don't like Santa bee
Holy down the chimney for me, boy boy
Scooby-Dooby-Dooby-Doo. It's the fact that the original is kind of sung with like a baby tone, like really... ugh
Yeah
Yeah, it ain't good, Scoob
Can I help you?
Hello?
Can't get me
I'm in the break room
Listen, I got no problem with Eartha Kitt
I love Eartha Kidd
I think Eartha Kitt's great
But I don't think Santa Baby is great
It was not a judgment on Eartha Kitt
I can hold two truths in my mind simultaneously
Do they know it's Christmas time is also atrocious? Yes
That one's atrocious on like a writing level
Yeah
And the fucking Christmas shoes one
Christmas shoes, Christmas shoes is like, whoever wrote that was like, Oh my God
I'm going to freaking rake it in with the money
Yeah
People are going to weep
It's like manipulative sad
Yeah
Which always pisses me off
I'm like, you're trying to make me sad and you haven't earned it
You have not earned my tears
You do like have a particular hate,
for like
sentimental commercials too
Yeah, because they haven't earned it
,Yeah, well, because
It feels like they're trying to manipulate me into feeling something so that I buy their fucking folders
They don't care if I feel something, they don't care about me. -They're not trying to say something that is true and real
They're just trying to say you too could have this moment where you don't understand if this person is dating or siblings
Um, buy this coffee
I'm just gonna go
Yeah, and then every iteration of Santa Baby, I don't like. -Like no one's improved on it. -No. -And that's like truly when you know,
No
You know a song is bad for two reasons. One, a legendary singer sung it and it's bad and you still don't like it
And other people have tried their takes on it and none of them have worked for you
I also want to say
If you like
Santa baby
Then get out!
You're fine to have that opinion?
You're a pervert
I just want to know
You're a nasty little freak
You've ruined my bit
Sorry, I thought I was trying to like do a bit with you
Well, I was going to go on like a whole thing about how you're like fine to have your opinions, but you're stupid for having it
but then you just said that they were stupid throughout the whole thing, and now I just feel like I'm bullying
I... there was a misinterpret. Can I tell you what happened?
Yeah,
I thought that you were going to say,
Something sincere like I usually do?
Something sincere like you usually do like that it is fine to like something that we don't like and you know all that kind of thing
because that's normally what I would say, yeah
That's normally what you would say. -And so I was like, it would be funny if I interspersed your sincere thing with being needlessly antagonistic
And then we'd be going back and forth with you sincere, me antagonistic. -I didn't realize you were doing an inversion on the formula
Yeah, yeah
And so I played in the wrong space
No, I understand where the miscommunication was
And for that, I apologize
I'm just saying you're an asshole
I
am going to resign
I'm going to resign
Normally
Normally, that is the bit that I do
Just sometimes
Well, it's not even a bit, you just don't want people to feel bad, which is nice
Yeah
Um, I do
I am trying to play with it though, you know?
Yeah
Interesting
This game sucks
How did they invent this game?
D and D? Just roll a 20
Get a crit
Wait, like my problem is that I can't see which one's being highlighted a lot of the time
I'm sorry
What are we trying to make here?
The thing that's on the wall
Sorry
It's like people in a boat and then the reflection of the boat
is how I'm seeing it
All right, just make that
Okay
OK, so that one's right
Yeah, that goes there
And then that one goes on the top. -Red goes on top, yeah, yeah, yeah. -Yes, yes, yes
Yes!
7-414, all right, that's like in the middle of it. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Hey, how's it going, ladies? I respect women, I called you ladies
Not bitches like I normally would
Hey
seven, four, one
I'm joking, I would never
The videotape!
The videotape
Okay
Excuse me
And the basement key
Yeah, I saw the door in the basement, is that that E?
the choir of angels sing their song
Have I been in here?
Okay, it just won't wash off, order new sheets, okay
When I get frustrated with laundry, that's how I feel too
jinkies
Thank you
It's fine, actually
Oh, it's not fun
James is about to go double haunted by watching the ring tape
Dude, what would happen if you watched the ring in Silent Hill?
And you brought in freaking Samara
What would she do here? Would it be like Sadako versus Kayako?
Whoa
Where they like pit them against each other
pyramid head versus
versus Samara
Samara?
Oh, I thought I could watch the VHS tape here
That was my mistake
Why would you think that because there's a TV that's on?
And that's like making noise actively
That's the elevator
Elevator, elevator, take me home. I saw the freaking basement! There it is
Sounds like sculpture, right? What's that?
It's okay, we're doing okay
Okay
Even here, huh?
Even here, even now
Hmm, that's unfortunate
No, I'm not
I'll go this way
It's Onsta's bee day, is this true?
Really?
Someone in chat said it, it has to be true
You can't say that if it's not true. -It is, oh my god, happy birthday to Onsta
Is Asta streaming?
Nasa's streaming
)We will... raid
We will raid and everyone will say happy birthday Onsta, every single one of you
Every single person that raids
Which better be everyone
Ding dong, ding dong
I guess if you ever find a save point, we'll
Damn, I was really hoping to finish Silent Hill tonight
Not that I'm not having a great time, just
You know, I've been wanting to play other things
I mean, unless you want to go late
I don't know how much longer we have is the problem
Ah
I was hoping they wouldn't scream
I'm getting reckless because I
I just... I'm like taking shortcuts now
Go ahead, James
He's pumping the valve
He's really slow at it
Probably a stream more
one stream more
Yeah.  One stream more
Roughly an hour left of game
Hmm
So we ain't finishing it now
The stress I felt picking a key off of a
machine over a grate
It's pretty
Pretty high
Every time I'm holding
our car keys slash apartment keys and we get in the elevator in our building
I'm like gripping those things so tight because there's like a crack this big
Yeah
between the elevator and the floor
And I'm like, one false move
And I drop those keys. -If I drop the keys, they're going right in there. -I know that for a fact. -They will not bounce. -They will nothing but net in the crack and be gone forever
Yeah
Come on, Jane
Why don't you... yeah
He wasn't ready
The Eddie slash James marriage cutscene is 35 minutes long, so be sure to account for that
Spoilers for the ending
Damn, ruining everything
It's a little wet in here, huh?
It's a little wet and wild. I've heard of a wet bar, but
Better leave
A millionth time James has gotten his shoes wet
His socks got to be soaked
I hate wet socks, man
The little mermaid figure, oh boy
That's unfortunate
The stream's over, bud
You don't need to think about those fish tackles
Oh
Are you okay?
I just wanted to finish today
No, we can't
There was too much game
There's too much, Julia, there's just too much game
just got lost a little less, maybe we could have done it
next time and then we'll have an hour to do something else
Now I look stupid for wearing this outfit again for the last stream. It's not even last stream
That is true, you do look stupid
, I look stupid
You look so stupid
I saved, right? I'm just going to save it
You look so dumb right now
Honestly, I've got the it
Because of how dumb you look
Well
Whoa
Is that the first time I've given you the yick?
I'm icked, I'm icked
Is that the first time?
No, I don't get the ick from you
because I love you
Whoa
Thanks for listening
I was just thinking about
phrases that we hate that's used on social media a lot, and for a while I didn't like the ick, but the one that's been like driving me up a wall is healing my inner child
Oh yeah
Anyway
It's because I keep getting it in ads
Yeah
They're like, this product really healed my inner child and I'm like, no, it fucking didn't
There's no child in there
You're an adult, there's not a child in there
Heal your adult self
Have fun. What you actually mean is that you had fun in your adult life, which is what you're supposed to be doing
You played with a Lego
Like just freaking do it. Play is really important as important to
Have fun as an adult. It's not illegal, do it, it's good for you
It's okay
Anyways, I'm going to read some subs and then we're going to raid Onsta
So that you can wish Onsta a happy birthday
Okay, I'm going to read subs now
Where's my what?
Beating the shit out of my inner child
This product really beat the shit out of my inner child
Okay, thank you for subscribing to
Us?
The letter S
,Wiggy Teo, Osaka Starling, Pork Waterfall, August Lesbian, Rando79, Primal Hunger,
Nikki of Time
,Jimmy Jam, Cryptid Space, Merlin Hurricane, A Pigeon Daddy, Allegretto, Blink Pop,
Modredastal, Procrasticrafting, Only Moose You Know, JT Barnett, Yash Power 2131, Spooky Kabuki, Sucre Baroque, Cybernetic Crime, Silver to Black, Abap, Abap, Abap, Abap, Abap,
Crit one cal failure, critical failure. The one's like an I, like it's like a number for a letter
TWest, SarahBearBaby, OllyCat24, GenderInnovator, JackAuburn, SuperHumanFoods,
,Sleepy Mr. Puddin', Tie Like Tea, Snored, Resident Goblin, Slorts S. Papa Zappa,
,Benny4 gifted five subs, thank you, Benny4
,ReBebop, Robibobody,
MothMith gifted five subs, thank you MothMith
Garden
Sorry, sorry to laugh again, this product gave my inner child the people's elbow
So specific
Garden Variety Necromancer, Yoinkie Zoinks, Twisted Cobalt, Shastadon28, Hannah Na, Avatar Cliffy, Miranda Grace gave out 30 subs
How did I didn't even see that? Thank you so much. Hot damn, 30 subs?
That is a big fat stack. 30 subs for my 30th birthday on Tuesday. Holy shit, happy birthday. And thank you so much. That's incredible, geez
,Digit18, WithSyrup, PunishedCrow, SturgeonBay,
Adventure Wren, Becca Anne, Damn Sam I Am, Bognosticator, For The Honor Of Gay, Cold Kinetic Heat,
,CatsRibs, ColinMelia, ValeHella, MaliciousMischief, BabySmack, AestheticallyBuy, GiveOutFive, GiftedSounds, oh, thank you
,Icky Necko, Yurt Gert, King123Frog, Johnny Guitar, Spencer's Avalanche, Professor Rad, Gifted10,
professorial subs, thank you, Professor Rad, as always
Hazel Cat, Heathcliffisaprat, Optimus Fine, Shadowman1188, Hibernation Dream, A Robots, Fancyfin99, TheNewBehive, TransriteSylveon, TiniestHands, NamelessNoodle, MothMith, CloudClovelierPrimary, Ruthifer,
And that is it for that. Let me go back to the top
Chubby Kraken, Ancient Arachnid,
OK, I think that is it
Thank you all so much, appreciate all of you
We're going to raid Onsta
watching and hanging, we are going to raid Onsta, say happy birthday to Onsta, but just say happy birthday, not like I said it
No, also someone asked what our favorite like Christmas cookie is. I think I'm just a gingerbread
sugar cookie lady
I don't eat cookies, I only eat chicken breast
I made sticky toffee pudding recently, it was pretty good
Yeah, she did a great job, it was delicious
I think that was my first sticky toffee pudding
OK, we're going to send you over to Onsta, say happy birthday. We'll see you tomorrow night on Drawfee stream. I think we are playing Mario Wonder
Oh yeah, and it's our last stream for the year
And it's our last dream of the year. -So get ready for some yelling at Mario and friends. -Goodbye, everyone
Bye!